Finding Aid for the John Egerton Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Subject Files (1970s)
  - Inequality in Education, # 12, July 1972 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Testing & Tracking: Bias in the Classroom, Inequality in Education, and # 14, July 1973 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Citizen Voices in the Public Schools, Inequality in Education, # 15, November 1973 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Discipline & Student Rights, Inequality in Education, # 20, July 1975 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Migrant Education, Inequality in Education, # 21, June 1976 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Integrated Education, July-August 1970, Vol. VIII, No. 4 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Integrated Education, March-April 1971, Vol. IX, No. 2 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Integrated Education, September-October 1971, Vol. IX, No. 5 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Integrated Education, November-December 1971, Vol. IX, No. 6 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Integrated Education, January-February 1972, Vol. X, No. 1 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Integrated Education, March-April 1972, Vol. X, No. 2 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Subject Files (1970s)
  - Our Promised Land, Southern Exposure, Fall 1974 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - No More Moanin’, Voices of Southern Struggle, Southern Exposure, Winter 1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Facing South, Southern Exposure, Winter 1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Guide to the Manuscripts & Archives in the Negro Collection of Trevor Arnett Library, Atlanta University, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Mexican-Americans and the Administration of Justice in the Southwest, March 1970-Report of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Title IV and School Desegregation, January 1973-Report of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - The Southwest Indian Report, May 1973-Report of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Research and Background Materials for proposed article on Charles Morgan-Interviews (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Research and Background Materials for proposed article on Charles Morgan-Articles (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Vanderbilt University’s Centennial Celebration, 1973-Commemorative Booklet, Handwritten Notes (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight, (The New York Times Magazine, Sept. 28, 1980)-Manuscript (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Manuscripts-Early Drafts (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Planning and Outlines (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Research and Background Materials-Articles & Tape (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Research and Background Materials-Newspaper Clippings (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Research and Background Materials-Photos (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Heritage of a Heavyweight-Publication Materials (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - TVA Nukes (The Progressive, Dec. 1980)-Manuscript (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - TVA Nukes-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Report to Percy (Cross Reference-Tennessee Committee for Humanities, Fall 1980)-Manuscript (2 copies) (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - International Education Programs at Western Kentucky University (Change, May 1980 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - International Education Programs at Western Kentucky University-Research and Background Materials- Articles (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Claude Pepper (The New York Times Magazine, Nov. 29, 1981)
  - Manuscript (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Planning and Outlines (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Research and Background Materials-Newspaper Clippings (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Research and Background Materials-Newspaper Clippings (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence-Incoming (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Boom or Bust in the Hollows of Appalachia (The New York Times Magazine, Oct. 18, 1981
  - Manuscript (2 Copies) (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Proof Copy (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Draft Copies (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Article excerpted from Boom or Bust in the Hollows of Appalachia (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Planning and Outlines (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Research and Background Materials-Newspaper Articles (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Research and Background Materials-Research Notes (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-Incoming (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Publication Materials-Payment (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - The Participation of Black Americans in Higher Education-A Report Sponsored by the Southern Education Foundation, 1981-Manuscript (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - The Participation of Black Americans in Higher Education-Conference Agenda & Participants (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - The Participation of Black Americans in Higher Education-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - The Participation of Black Americans in Higher Education-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - The Participation of Black Americans in Higher Education-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - The Participation of Black Americans in Higher Education-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - The Participation of Black Americans in Higher Education-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - A Big Job for a Little Town (The Progressive, April 1981)-Manuscript (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - A Big Job for a Little Town-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - A Big Job for a Little Town-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - A Big Job for a Little Town-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - A Big Job for a Little Town-Research and Background Materials-Research Notes (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - A Big Job for a Little Town-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Tennessee: Seizing Opportunity (Fortune, May 1981)-Manuscript (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee: Seizing Opportunity-Manuscript-Typewritten Draft Copies (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Tennessee: Seizing Opportunity-Planning and Outlines (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee: Seizing Opportunity-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes and Interviews (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Tennessee: Seizing Opportunity-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Tennessee: Seizing Opportunity-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Tennessee: Seizing Opportunity-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Appalachia’s Absentee Landlords (The Progressive, June 1981)-Manuscript (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Appalachia’s Absentee Landlords-Planning and Outlines (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Appalachia’s Absentee Landlords-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Appalachia’s Absentee Landlords-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project (1981)-Manuscript (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Planning and Outlines (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Research and Background Materials-ACE/Aspen Institute Seminar on the Desegregation of Higher Education (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Research and Background Materials-Newspaper Clippings (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - American Council on Education Desegregation Project-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - College Board Test Project (1981)-Manuscript (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - College Board Test Project-Planning and Outlines (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - College Board Test Project-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - College Board Test Project-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - College Board Test Project-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - College Board Test Project-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - College Board Test Project-Research and Background Materials-Test Materials (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - College Board Test Project-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - College Board Test Project-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Patrick County (VA) Project (1982)-Manuscript (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Patrick County (VA) Project-Planning and Outlines (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Patrick County (VA) Project-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Patrick County (VA) Project-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Patrick County (VA) Project-Research and Background Materials-Patrick County Project Impact Series Scripts (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Patrick County (VA) Project-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Lakeland Wesley Village (1982)-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Lakeland Wesley Village-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Lakeland Wesley Village-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Lakeland Wesley Village-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Notes from a School Watcher’s Journal (The Progressive, March 1982)-Manuscript (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Notes from a School Watcher’s Journal-Planning and Outlines (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Notes from a School Watcher’s Journal-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Notes from a School Watcher’s Journal-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Notes from a School Watcher’s Journal-Research and Background Materials-Related Articles by John Egerton (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Notes from a School Watcher’s Journal-Research and Background Materials-Newspaper Clippings (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Notes from a School Watcher’s Journal-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Notes from a School Watcher’s Journal-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Washington Post Columns (1982)-Manuscripts (Porch Talk, Workspace, Moving, Compensation) (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Washington Post Columns-Planning and Outlines (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Washington Post Columns-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Washington Post Columns-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Washington Post Columns-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Breathitt County Schools (Education Week, 1982)-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Breathitt County Schools-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Breathitt County Schools-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Summertime in Tortola: Living Is Easy (The New York Times Magazine, August 29, 1982)-Manuscript (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Summertime in Tortola: Living Is Easy-Planning and Outlines (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Summertime in Tortola: Living Is Easy-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Summertime in Tortola: Living Is Easy-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Summertime in Tortola: Living Is Easy-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Summertime in Tortola: Living Is Easy-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Summertime in Tortola: Living Is Easy-Publication Materials (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Nashville (Booklet for the Chamber of Commerce, 1982)-Manuscript (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Nashville-Manuscript-Proof Copy (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Nashville-Manuscript-Typescript (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Nashville-Planning and Outlines (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Nashville-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Nashville- Correspondence-Incoming (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Southern Books at Home on Campus (Southern Exposure, Jan./Feb. 1983)-Manuscript (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Southern Books at Home on Campus-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Southern Books at Home on Campus-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Southern Books at Home on Campus-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Southern Books at Home on Campus-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Highlander’s 50th Anniversary (Community Jobs, 1983)-Manuscript (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Highlander’s 50th Anniversary-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Highlander’s 50th Anniversary-Research and Background Materials-Articles And Tapes (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Highlander’s 50th Anniversary-Research and Background Materials-Photographs And Tape (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Highlander’s 50th Anniversary-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - A Case of Prejudice: Maurice Mays and the Knoxville Race Riot of 1919 (Southern Exposure, July/August, 1983)-Manuscript (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - A Case of Prejudice-Manuscript-Galley Proofs (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - A Case of Prejudice-Manuscript-Typescript (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - A Case of Prejudice-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - A Case of Prejudice-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - A Case of Prejudice-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - A Case of Prejudice-Research and Background Materials-Newspaper Clippings (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - A Case of Prejudice-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - A Case of Prejudice-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Nissan in Tennessee (October 1983)-Manuscript (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Nissan in Tennessee-Manuscript-Galley Proofs (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Nissan in Tennessee-Manuscript-Xerox Copy of Typescript (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Unions in Tennessee (USA Today, January 1983)-Planning and Outlines (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Unions in Tennessee-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Unions in Tennessee-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Unions in Tennessee-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Workers Take Over the Store (The New York Times Magazine, September 11, 1983)
  - Manuscript (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript-Proof Copy (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Planning and Outlines (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Research and Background Materials-Newspaper Clippings (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-Incoming (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Publication Materials (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Generations (1983)
  - Manuscript-Chapters1-3 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript-Chapters4-6 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript-Chapters7-9 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript-Chapters10-12 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript-Chapters13-15 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript-Chapters16-18 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript-First Draft Typescript, Book 1 (Chapters1-5, Spring) (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript-First Draft Typescript, Book 2 (Chapters 6-9, Summer) (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript-First Draft Typescript, Book 3 (Chapters 10-13, Fall) (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript-First Draft Typescript, Book 4 (Chapters 14-16, Winter) (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Generations (1983)
  - Manuscript-Typescript, Book 1 (Chapters 1-5, Spring) (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript-Typescript, Book 2 (Chapters 6-9, Summer) (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript-Typescript, Book 3 (Chapters 10-13, Fall) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript-Typescript, Book 4 (Chapters 14-16, Winter) (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Generations (1983)
  - Manuscript-Japanese Edition (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Planning and Outlines (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Background and Research Materials-Newspaper Clippings (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Background and Research Materials-Articles (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Background and Research Materials-Articles (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Background and Research Materials-Phone Books for Harlan, KY & Lancaster, KY (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Background and Research Materials-Research Notes, Typed & Handwritten (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Generations (1983)
  - Background and Research Materials-Research Notes, Handwritten (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Background and Research Materials-Research Notes, Handwritten (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Background and Research Materials-Research Notes, Handwritten (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Background and Research Materials-Maps (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Background and Research Materials-Maps (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Background and Research Materials-Genealogical Lists (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Background and Research Materials-Data Provided by and Correspondence with Charles Ledford (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Generations (1983)
  - Edited Transcripts of Ledford Tapes
    - Background and Research Materials-C.B. & Addie Ledford, 3/14/78-8/17/78 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Background and Research Materials-C.B. & Addie Ledford, 8/17/78-12/18/78 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Background and Research Materials-C.B. & Addie Ledford, 7/24/79-3/5/80 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Matilda L. King & Daughter, 5/28/78 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: C.B. Ledford, Jr., 7/19/78 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Jennie L. McLendon, 7/20/78 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Background and Research Materials-Anita W. Ledford, ex-wife of Bruce Ledford, Deceased-720/78 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Herbert R. Ledford & wife, Hazel Ledford, 8/3/78 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Edwin C. Ledford & wife, Geraldine Ledford, 8/3/78 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Lucille L. Smith, 8/17/78 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Dorothy L. Jackson, 8/17/78 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Matilda L. King, 9/4/78 and Eloise L. Beatty, 10/6/78 & 10/29/78 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Gwen L. Gastineau & husband, Russell Gastineau; also Richard & Adrienne Gastineau & Rebecca Gastineau, 12/18/78 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Background and Research Materials-Children: Mary Helen (Dolly) L. Casey, 7/20/78 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Background and Research Materials-Grandchildren: Jerry (Pop) Ledford, 8/18/78; Garry Hammon, 9/3/78; Becky Eversman, 9/3/78 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Background and Research Materials-Grandchildren: Billy Jack Ledford, 9/4/78; Sally L. Watkins, 9/13/78; Edwin Ledford & Steve Ledford, 9/13/78 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Background and Research Materials-Grandchildren: Emily L. Lawrence, 9/14/78; Jane L. Shelton, 9/26/78; Polly Hawkins, 10/4/78 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Background and Research Materials-Grandchildren: Sarah Ledford, 10/19/78; Nancy Allen, 10/19/78; Charlie Bob Ledford, 10/20/78 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Background and Research Materials-Grandchildren: Richard Ledford, 10/20/78; Judy Ledford, 10/20/78 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Background and Research Materials-Arletta Bourne, 10/29/78; Alice L. Fields, 11/8/78; Polly L. Hawkins, 11/15/78 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Background and Research Materials-Grandchildren: David Smith, 11/16/78; David Gastineau, 12/17/78 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Background and Research Materials-Grandchildren: Carole Gastineau Starnes, 12/18/78; Michael Ledford, 7/24/79; Sue L. Rudd, 8/25/79 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Background and Research Materials-Grandchildren: Polly Hawkins’ Taped Interviews with C.B. & Addie Ledford, 1976 & 1977 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Background and Research Materials-Interviews with Persons Not Members of the Immediate Family: Helen & Henry Pope (relatives), 8/18/78; Martha Nolan, Addie’s half-sister), 10/4/78 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Generations (1983)
  - Correspondence-Business-Contract Negotiations-Outgoing (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence-Business-Contract Incoming-Incoming (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Business-Subsidiary Rights-Outgoing (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-Business-Subsidiary Rights-Incoming (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-Business-Video Project-Outgoing (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-Business-Video Project-Incoming (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence-Business-Promotions-Outgoing (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-Business-Promotions-Incoming (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-Personal-Outgoing (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence-Personal-Incoming (A-H) (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-Personal-Incoming (K-Y) (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Publication Materials-Contracts (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Generations (1983)
  - Book Reviews-Journals (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Book Reviews-Journal (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Book Reviews-Newspapers (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Materials-Advertising, Personal Appearances (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Materials-Photographs (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Related Articles (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Generations (1983)
  - Tapes, Box 1
    - Row 1
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 3/14/78 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 3/15/78 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 3/15 & 3/16/78 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 4/10/78 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 4/11/78 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 5/27/78 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Tillie Ledford King and daughter, Barbara Jo Bryant, 5/28/78 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - C.B. Ledford, Jr., 7/19/78 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - C.B. Ledford, Jr., 7/19/78 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Jennie Ledford McLendon, 7/20/78 (Box 54, Folder 10)